Ryo Suzuki

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ryo-suzuki-598040175/

Professional Summary

Professional software developer with 4+ years of experience and extensive knowledge of the software development life-cycle.

In my last position, as a senior engineer in backend team, I did everything I could to improve the productivity of my team.

For example, I popularized testing, taught many things need to know to our members, and built a CI/CD pipeline so that we could release high-quality applications quickly.

Work Experience

Full-stack Developer

EISYS, Inc.

Feb 2020 - Mar 2022

• TODO

Full-stack Developer

Freelance

Feb 2019 - Jan 2020

• TODO

Full-stack Developer

fullout, Inc.

Mar 2018 - Feb 2019

• TODO

Education

Lakehead University, Vancouver, BC

Technical Skills

Experience in TODO, and Software Engineering. Tools:

• Data Science: R, Python with NumPy and Pandas, Spark (prior experience)

• Programming Technologies: SQL, MATLAB, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Java, JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Projects

TODO